<Document>
  # Path of Flesh
  The [color=firebrick]Path of Flesh[/color] focuses on summoning player-controlled [color=firebrick]Demons[/color] and creating [color=firebrick]Ghouls[/color] from corpses to do your bidding.

  Heretics on this path gain almost no offensive or defensive abilities, relying heavily on their servants to do the heavy lifting.

  Despite this, it allows for one to create an army of armed meat shields, making it a decent first path overall for inexperienced Heretics.

  [color=#8f63e6]Ascending[/color] allows you to shed your human form and become something much greater.

  ##Abilities
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticBladeFlesh" Caption="Principle of Hunger"/>
  </Box>
  Opens up the [color=firebrick]Path of Flesh[/color] to you.

  Allows you to transmute a knife and a pool of blood into a [color=red]Bloody Blade[/color].

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticIconGrasp" Caption="Grasp of Flesh"/>
  </Box>
  Your [color=green]Mansus Grasp[/color] gains the ability to create [color=firebrick]Ghouls[/color] from corpses.

  [color=firebrick]Ghouls[/color] look like corpses to heathens' eyes and typically only have 50 health, but can use [color=red]Bloody Blades[/color] effectively.

  Be warned, this ability, when performed, is highly visible to those around you.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="FoodPoppy" Caption="Imperfect Recipe"/>
  </Box>
  Allows you to transmute a humanoid corpse and a poppy to create a [color=firebrick]Voiceless Dead[/color].

  [color=firebrick]Voiceless Dead[/color] are mute [color=firebrick]Ghouls[/color], who typically only have 100 health, but can use [color=red]Bloody Blades[/color] effectively.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticIconGrasp" Caption="Mark of Flesh"/>
  </Box>
  Your [color=green]Mansus Grasp[/color] now applies the [color=firebrick]Mark of Flesh[/color]. The mark is triggered from an attack with your [color=red]Bloody Blade[/color].

  When triggered, its target begins to bleed heavily, before jumping to a new target.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticIconSurgery" Caption="Knitting of Flesh"/>
  </Box>
  Grants you the spell [color=firebrick]Knit Flesh[/color]. This spell causes a random effect to its target, between blinding, muting, and causing the target to vomit profusely.

  This spell also allows you to heal your servants, with a long do-after, making it ineffective in the heat of battle.

  This spell requires a [color=#8f63e6]Focus[/color] to cast.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MobGhoulProphet" Caption="Raw Ritual"/>
  </Box>
  Allows you to transmute a pair of eyes, a stomach, and a pool of blood to create a [color=firebrick]Raw Prophet[/color].

  [color=firebrick]Raw Prophets[/color] can jaunt, have the ability to link minds to communicate with ease, and have a powerful laser eye, which can burn your opponents.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticBladeFlesh" Caption="Bleeding Steel"/>
  </Box>
  Your [color=red]Bloody Blade[/color] now causes enemies to bleed heavily on attack, even more so when combined with your [color=firebrick]Mark of Flesh[/color].

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MobGhoulStalker" Caption="Lonely Ritual"/>
  </Box>
  Allows you to transmute a heart, a stomach, a pair of lungs, and a pen to create a [color=firebrick]Stalker[/color].

  [color=firebrick]Stalkers[/color] can jaunt, release EMPs, and are overall strong in combat.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticIconHymn" Caption="Priest’s Final Hymn"/>
  </Box>
  The [color=#8f63e6]Ascension[/color] ritual of the [color=firebrick]Path of Flesh[/color].

  Bring 4 corpses to a [color=#8f63e6]Transmutation Rune[/color] to complete the ritual.

  When completed, you gain the ability to shed your human form and become the [color=firebrick]Lord of the Night[/color], a supremely powerful creature.

  While in the [color=firebrick]Lord of the Night[/color] form, you can consume the living to heal and are able to devour walls and airlocks alike, much like a Space Dragon.

  Your melee attacks in this form are very powerful, doing a large amount of blunt damage, and being able to hit many targets at once.
</Document>
