<Document>
  # Path of Void
  The [color=steelblue]Path of Void[/color] focuses on stealth, silence and the freezing cold.

  While it offers very little utility early on, Heretics on this path quickly gain the ability to silence and freeze their victims, opening the window to silently ambush targets with no other items or chemicals required.

  This path has access to many strong transmuted items, but requires smart use to realize their full potential, making it moderately difficult for beginners.

  [color=#8f63e6]Ascending[/color] silences those around you, allows you to pass through windows, and gives you full immunity to the effects of space.

  ##Abilities
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticBladeVoid" Caption="Glimmer of Winter"/>
  </Box>
  Opens up the [color=steelblue]Path of Void[/color] to you.

  Allows you to transmute a knife in sub-zero temperatures into a [color=red]Void Blade[/color].

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticIconGrasp" Caption="Grasp of Void"/>
  </Box>
  Your [color=green]Mansus Grasp[/color] will temporarily mute and chill its target.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticIconWay" Caption="Aristocrat's Way"/>
  </Box>
  Grants you immunity to cold temperatures, and removes your need to breathe; however, you can still take damage due to a lack of pressure.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticIconGrasp" Caption="Mark of Void"/>
  </Box>
  Your [color=green]Mansus Grasp[/color] now applies the [color=steelblue]Mark of Void[/color]. The mark is triggered from an attack with your [color=red]Void Blade[/color].

  When triggered, it further silences the target and swiftly lowers the temperature of their body and the air around them.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticIconVoidBlast" Caption="Void Blast"/>
  </Box>
  Grants you [color=steelblue]Void Blast[/color], a spell that shoots out a freezing blast in a cone in front of you, freezing the ground and anyone within.

  This spell requires a [color=#8f63e6]Focus[/color] to cast.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticIconPhase" Caption="Void Phase"/>
  </Box>
  Grants you [color=steelblue]Void Phase[/color], a long range teleport spell.

  Additionally, this ability stuns heathens around your original location and target destination.

  This spell requires a [color=#8f63e6]Focus[/color] to cast.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticBladeVoid" Caption="Seeking Blade"/>
  </Box>
  Your [color=red]Void Blade[/color] chills its target on hit.

  Additionally, when a target is marked by your [color=steelblue]Mark of Void[/color], you can activate a [color=red]Void Blade[/color] in your hand to teleport next to them, without breaking the blade.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticIconPull" Caption="Void Pull"/>
  </Box>
  Grants you [color=steelblue]Void Pull[/color], a spell that pulls all nearby heathens towards you, stunning them briefly.

  This spell requires a [color=#8f63e6]Focus[/color] to cast.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticIconWaltz" Caption="Waltz at the End of Time"/>
  </Box>
  The [color=#8f63e6]Ascension[/color] ritual of the [color=steelblue]Path of Void[/color].

  Bring 3 corpses to a [color=#8f63e6]Transmutation Rune[/color] in sub-zero temperatures to complete the ritual.

  When completed, it grants you the [color=steelblue]Aristocrat's Blessing[/color]. Walls around you will be turned to ice, and the air will constantly be frozen. Along with this, you are able to walk through things like glass and railings, and lasers cannot hit you.

  Additionally, you will become immune to the effects of space.
</Document>
