<Document>
  # Path of Hunt
  The [color=yellowgreen]Path of Hunt[/color] focuses on gunplay and tangible items, and comes highly recommended for first-time Heretics.

  It's very strong in its comfort zone - which is to say, far away from its prey - but flounders in close-combat situations.

  It offers many powerful tools which will allow you to use your guns far more effectively than heathens.

  [color=#8f63e6]Ascending[/color] will make you reflect any and all projectiles that hit you.

  ##Abilities
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponRevolverSerpentine" Caption="Principle of Strife"/>
  </Box>
  Opens up the [color=yellowgreen]Path of Hunt[/color] to you.

  Allows you to transmute a pistol and a knife into a [color=red]Serpentine Revolver[/color]. Makeshift Pistols and Flare Guns will both suffice.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticIconGrasp" Caption="Hunter's Grasp"/>
  </Box>
  Your [color=green]Mansus Grasp[/color] gains the ability to refill an empty bullet casing.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticIconTower" Caption="Watchtower Striving"/>
  </Box>
  Grants you the [color=yellowgreen]Watchtower Striving[/color] spell, which places a tower that redirects bullets towards heathens when hit.

  This spell requires a [color=#8f63e6]Focus[/color] to cast.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticIconGrasp" Caption="Mark of Hunt"/>
  </Box>
  Your [color=green]Mansus Grasp[/color] will cause your prey to be slowed for a short time.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticAmmoPouch" Caption="Meteoric Pouch"/>
  </Box>
  Grants a ritual that allows you to transmute a pill canister and a pipe into a [color=red]Meteoric Pouch[/color], which works as a portable ammo fabricator.

  A [color=red]Meteoric Pouch[/color] produces [color=red]Meteoric Bullets[/color], which phase through walls.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticIconFocus" Caption="Serpent's Focus"/>
  </Box>
  Grants you the [color=yellowgreen]Serpent's Focus[/color] ability, which allows you to see living things through walls, but blacks out your vision.

  This spell requires a [color=#8f63e6]Focus[/color] to cast.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponSniperLionhunter" Caption="Lion's Bane"/>
  </Box>
  Grants a ritual that allows you to transmute a pistol, some meat, and a pair of eyes into a [color=red]Lionhunter's Rifle[/color].

  The [color=red]Lionhunter's Rifle[/color] comes full of .60 meteoric bullets, and has long-range sniper sights.

  When paired with the [color=yellowgreen]Serpent's Focus[/color] ability, the user can cause extreme damage from a safe, hidden position.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticSkaptodonCloak" Caption="Warden's Shroud"/>
  </Box>
  Grants a ritual that allows you to transmute a scarf, a glass shard, and a brain into a [color=red]Skaptodon Cloak[/color], which allows the wearer to become invisible while still.

  The [color=red]Skaptodon Cloak[/color] can be active for two minutes on a full charge, and needs to be turned off for a short time before it will begin to recharge.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="KitchenSpike" Caption="Manhunt's Reversal"/>
  </Box>
  The [color=#8f63e6]Ascension[/color] ritual of the [color=yellowgreen]Path of Hunt[/color].

  Bring 3 handcuffed corpses to a [color=#8f63e6]Transmutation Rune[/color] to complete the ritual.

  This ritual will complete your transformation from Prey to [color=yellowgreen]Hunter[/color]. You will redirect all projectiles that hit you back at your foes. However, you can still be hurt by melee weapons and lasers.
</Document>
