<Document>
  # Path of Ash
  The [color=tomato]Path of Ash[/color] revolves around fire, mobility, and crowd control. It grants many powerful tools, but they come with the risk of burning in your own flames.

  This path is powerful, yet risky. [color=#8f63e6]Ascending[/color] gives you the power to burn down the station in a living tornado of flame.

  ##Abilities
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticBladeAsh" Caption="Nightwatcher's Secret"/>
  </Box>
  Opens up the [color=tomato]Path of Ash[/color] to you.

  Allows you to transmute a welding tool and a knife into an [color=red]Ashen Blade[/color].

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticIconGrasp" Caption="Grasp of Ash"/>
  </Box>
  Your [color=green]Mansus Grasp[/color] will burn the eyes of the victim, blurring their vision.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticIconDash" Caption="Blazing Dash"/>
  </Box>
  Grants you [color=tomato]Blazing Dash[/color], a spell that lets you move extremely quickly for a short time, while setting you ablaze.

  Be sure to bring a firesuit and something to extinguish yourself with- you'll be on fire for the whole duration of the dash and some time afterwards.

  This spell requires a [color=#8f63e6]Focus[/color] to cast.
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticIconGrasp" Caption="Mark of Ash"/>
  </Box>
  Your [color=green]Mansus Grasp[/color] now applies the [color=tomato]Mark of Ash[/color]. The mark is triggered from an attack with your [color=red]Ashen Blade[/color].

  When triggered, its target is set ablaze and takes a large amount of stamina damage, before jumping to a new target.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticIconFlameBlast" Caption="Volcanic Blast"/>
  </Box>
  Grants you [color=tomato]Volcanic Blast[/color], a spell that fires a ball of flame at the nearest heathen.

  Upon successfully hitting its target, the fireball divides into multiple smaller fireballs targeting other nearby heathens.

  This spell requires a [color=#8f63e6]Focus[/color] to cast.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingMaskMadHeretic" Caption="Mask of Madness"/>
  </Box>
  Allows you to transmute any mask, four candles, a stun baton, and a liver to create a [color=red]Mask of Madness[/color].

  The mask instills fear into heathens who witness it, causing stamina damage, hallucinations, and insanity.

  It cannot be taken off without outside help, for Heretic and heathen alike.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticBladeAsh" Caption="Fiery Blade"/>
  </Box>
  Your [color=red]Ashen Blade[/color] now lights enemies aflame on attack.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticIconRebirth" Caption="Nightwatcher's Rebirth"/>
  </Box>
  Grants you [color=tomato]Nightwatcher's Rebirth[/color], a spell that extinguishes you and burns all nearby heathens who are currently on fire, healing you for every victim afflicted.

  If any victims afflicted are in critical condition, they will instantly die.

  This spell requires a [color=#8f63e6]Focus[/color] to cast.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HereticIconOath" Caption="Ashlord's Rite"/>
  </Box>
  The ascension ritual of the [color=tomato]Path of Ash[/color].

  Bring 3 burning corpses to a [color=#8f63e6]Transmutation Rune[/color] to complete the ritual.

  When completed, you become a [color=tomato]Harbinger of Flames[/color], gaining a new ability, [color=tomato]Oath of Flame[/color], which sets you ablaze and causes you to passively create a ring of flames as you walk.

  You will also become immune to flames, space, and similar environmental hazards.
</Document>
